http://www.artsdel.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - ArtsDel
Toppics
Electronics
Wifi Speaker Wifi Repeater Wifi Printer Trail Camera Photo Printer Laser Printer 3D Pen 3D Printer 3D Printers in Art Slide Scanner Barcode Scanner Label Maker Label Printer Green Screen Background Wifi Radio 4K Projector Portable Projector Android Car Stereo Android Endoscope Android Projector Android Tv Box Atomic Watch Bluetooth Receiver Bug Zappers Cable Modem Headphone Amplifier Cell Phone Signal Booster Laser Cutter Engraver Laptop Docking Station Liquid Cpu Cooler Electric Knife Teleprompter Electric Pencil Sharpener Garage Door Opener Geiger Counter Heat Press Machine Money Counter Electric Pencil Sharpener Rechargeable Hand Warmer Monitor Privacy Screen
Household
Foam Mattress Electric Water Heater Electric Knife Sharpener Portable Ice Maker Projection Alarm Clock Ultrasonic Cleaners Airbrush Cake Decorating
Sport-Leisure
Yoga Mat Bag Yoga Mat Trekking Backpack Hiking Backpack 1 Person Tent 2 Person Tent 3 Person Tent Trampoline Ping Pong Table Electric Skateboard Electronic Dart Board Electric Scooter Air Hockey Table Gopro Gimbal
Musical Instruments
Digital Piano Electric Guitar
Baby Toddler
Crib Mattress Toddler mattress Kids Trampoline
Garden
Well Pump Sprinkler Systems Controllers Zero Turn Mower
Beauty
Hair dryer Hair Clipper
Blog
Painting for kids What is Art? 3D Printers in Art
Select Page
Privacy Policy:
ArtsDel (“ArtsDel“) operates artsdel.org and may operate other websites. It is ArtsDel’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, ArtsDel collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ArtsDel’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ArtsDel’s visitors use its website. From time to time, ArtsDel may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
ArtsDel also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on artsdel.org blogs/sites. ArtsDel only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to ArtsDel’s websites choose to interact with ArtsDel in ways that require ArtsDel to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ArtsDel gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at artsdel.org to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with ArtsDel are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, ArtsDel collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with ArtsDel. ArtsDel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
ArtsDel may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. ArtsDel may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ArtsDel does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
ArtsDel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ArtsDel’s behalf or to provide services available at ArtsDel’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ArtsDel’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ArtsDel will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ArtsDel discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when ArtsDel believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ArtsDel, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an ArtsDel website and have supplied your email address, ArtsDel may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with ArtsDel and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ArtsDel takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ArtsDel uses cookies to help ArtsDel identify and track visitors, their usage of ArtsDel website, and their website access preferences. ArtsDel visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ArtsDel’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of ArtsDel’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If ArtsDel, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that ArtsDel goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of ArtsDel may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ArtsDel and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, ArtsDel may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ArtsDel’s sole discretion. ArtsDel encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a artsdel.org account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Related Posts:Monitor Privacy ScreenprivacyPrivacy filmBalcony privacyGarden Privacy ScreenTerms of Service
Read Also about:
welcome page Electronics Beauty Baby Toddler Garden Sport-Leisure Musical Instruments Privacy Policy Terms of Service AMAZON DISCLOSURE Household Delaware Division of the Arts
ArtsDel.org is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.
Privacy Policy | Terms of Service
